

-Falling Away From Me / Afastando-se de Mim
É considerada a melhor música do álbum Issues, e muitas vezes até a melhor música do KoЯn

-Hey, I'm feeling tired, my time is gone today
Ei, estou me sentindo cansado, meu tempo se foi hoje
-You flirt with suicide, sometimes that's ok
Você flerta com suicídio, às vezes está tudo bem
-Do what others say, I'm here standing hollow
Faça o que os outros mandam, estou aqui me sentindo vazio
-Falling away from me, falling away from me
Afastando-se de mim, afastando-se de mim

-Day is here fading, that's when I'm insane
-I flirt with suicide, sometimes kill the pain
-I can always say, it's gonna be better tomorrow
Eu sempre posso dizer, será melhor amanhã
-Falling away from me, falling away from me

-Beating me down, beating me, beating me down
Me batendo, me batendo, me batendo
-Down into the ground
-Screaming so sound, beating me, beating me down
-Down into the ground

-(Falling away from me)
-It's spinning round and round
-(Falling away from me)
-It's lost and can't be found
-(Falling away from me)
-It's spinning round and round
-(Falling away from me)
-So it down

-Beating me down, beating me, beating me down
-Down into the ground
-Screaming so sound, beating me, beating me down
-Down into the ground

-Twisting me, they won't go away
-So I pray, go away

-Life's falling away from me
A vida está se afastando de mim
-It's falling away from me
Está se afastando de mim
-Life's falling away from me
A vida está se afastando de mim
-Fuck!

-Beating me down, beating me, beating me down
-Down into the ground
-Screaming so sound, beating me, beating me down
-Down into the ground

-Beating me down, beating me, beating me down
-Down into the ground
-Screaming so sound, beating me, beating me down
-Down into the ground