Super Mario Kart

Versões Originais :
Americana
Europeu
Japonesa

----Ferramentas :
Speedometer ( E, U e J )
----Modificadas / Hackeadas :
Super Mario Kart [J] Turbo (NTSC)
A Super Mario Kart Japanese Version Turbo Hack. You have infinite Mushroom.

Super Mario Kart [E] GP150cc Training (PAL)
A Super Mario Kart European Version Hack for GP150cc Record practicing. Speedometer is integreted, GP150cc and Special Cup are unlocked, Items probabilities have been modified to get only good items for Shortuts and Long Boosts.

Super Mario Kart [U] GP150cc Training (NTSC)
A Super Mario Kart American Version Hack for GP150cc Record practicing. Speedometer is integreted, GP150cc and Special Cup are unlocked, Items probabilities have been modified to get only good items for Shortuts and Long Boosts.

Super Mario Kart [E] All Modes 150cc (PAL)
A Super Mario Kart European Version Hack by smkdan where you can select 50cc, 100cc or 150cc for all of the 4 SMK modes (Battle Mode, Match Race, Time Trial, and Grand Prix)

Super Mario Kart [U] All Modes 150cc (NTSC)
A Super Mario Kart American Version Hack by smkdan where you can select 50cc, 100cc or 150cc for all of the 4 SMK modes (Battle Mode, Match Race, Time Trial, and Grand Prix)

Super Mario Kart [U] Balloon Hack (NTSC)
A Super Mario Kart American Version Hack by smkdan where you can select the number of balloons you will have in Battle Mode.

Super Mario Kart [U] Items Hack (NTSC)
A Super Mario Kart American Version Hack by smkdan on which there is a startup menu that allows you to select infinite items' for both player 1 and player 2. .

new tracks:
Super Parigo Kart (PAL)
A complete hack made by ScouB featuring new characters (from the SMK Championships community), 20 new tracks with working AI, 4 new battle arenas, new graphics, etc... 

Super Parigo Kart 2 (PAL)
The sequel of Super Parigo Kart, still made by ScouB, featuring 20 new tracks with working AI, 4 new battle arenas.

Mario Kart R (NTSC)
A complete hack made by d4s! featuring Kirby replacing Toad, 20 new tracks with working AI, 4 new battle arenas, new graphics, etc...

Reverse Mario Kart (NTSC)
The same tracks than Super Mario Kart but driven in reverse mode, hack made by Lightfoot! and ShadowSMK! Some small adjustments have been made to the tracks to make the driving smoother and to enjoy new shortcuts.

Super Mario Kart 2 (NTSC)
20 new tracks and 4 new battle arenas.

Super Mario Kart 3 (NTSC)
20 new tracks made by Sylvain.

Super Mario Kart 4 (NTSC)
20 new tracks and 3 new battle arenas made by Sylvain.

Super Mario Kart 5 (NTSC)
20 new tracks and 4 new battle arenas made by KartSeven.

----Outras :

200,250 e 300cc = Minha versão , é apenas 1 rom original com mais 240 de velocidade máxima pros carros ( Pra entender veja esse link : https://quase1otaku.blogspot.com/2019/06/curiosidades-smk-quanto-vale-50cc.html )
8
Alternative Track 
Baldy Kart 
Botsu = Parte 11,19
By FTR 
By NandoPro 
Character Chaos 
Crazy Tracks 
Crazy Tracks 2 = Parte 15
Devanny Dark 
Epic Tio Kart = Parte 14
SMK - F1 Tracks by MarioDesigner 4.0 

Hardmode = Parte 12
Hyper Street Kart
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VllZRwH40O4

Iniciante = É minha rom com pistas modificadas , talvez demore muito a sair porque eu to editando aos poucos e vou começar uma série aqui também no blog falando sobre isso
Metakarting = Parte 17
More Super Mario Kart 
N64 mode 
Parigo Kart
Parigo Kart 2 
Pro Edition
Pro Kart 
R1 
Reversed
Simple Kart = Parte 18
Simple Kart 2 = Parte 16
Simple Kart 3 = Parte 20
SMK 2, 3 , 4 and 5 
SMK-SNEstatalgia-2018 
SNEStalgia_2018_DEMO 
SourMusic Kart 
Spongebobkart 
Super Mister Doom Kart 
Super Simple Kart 1 , 2 and 3
Sylvain 150cc colored Complete 8 7 16 
Teletubies 
Tio Kart 
Tio Kart 2 
Tio Kart Rewheeled 
Universe 1 v1.0 (2010)

Japanese Hacks ( Need of Rom Japan ) 

マリオカート64逆リメイク 
マリオカートダブルダッシュ逆リメイク 
スーパーニコニコカート 
キャラクターカオス化 
没コース

Kaizo 

シリーズ1　 
シリーズ2　 
シリーズ3　 
シリーズ4